Guide to the Walter Isard papers, 1938-1986.
Isard, Walter papers
- WI Paper--The Predohl Contribution, July 1963, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 17)
- Summary Paper--Caracas, Nov. 1962--1st Latin American Regional Science Congress, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 18)
- Zurich Summary Paper with M. Th--Political Action & Techniques, Sept. 1962, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 19)
- I-O--Geneva Paper 1961, 1961 (Box 56, Folder 20)
- Isard + Reiner--Doxiadis Lecture 1961, 1961 (Box 56, Folder 21)
- WI Paper w/ Deutch Effective Distance (Box 56, Folder 22)
- Isard + Smolensky, I.O Paper--Geneva 1961, 1961 (Box 56, Folder 23)
- Isard & Stevens Paper LP 1961 for Zimmerman, 1961 (Box 56, Folder 24)
- AIR--RSA Session: Oct. 1960, Philadelphia, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 25)
- Urban Complex IGU Lund 1960, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 26)
- Notes on "Use of Regional Science Methods in Economic History", Economic History Assoc.--Sept. 1960, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 27)
- ISEA/RSA Paper Isard & Smolensky, June 1960 Paris--Recent Developments in Regional Science (Box 56, Folder 28)
- General Interregional Equilibrium Paper (Box 56, Folder 29)
- Scope & Nature of RS--Presidential Address, Dec. 1959, 1959 (Box 56, Folder 30)
- AAG Pittsburgh, Spring 1959, 1959 (Box 56, Folder 31)
- Nature & Scope of Regional Science--Dec. 1959, 1959 (Box 56, Folder 32)
- Is American Industry Moving to New Locations? AFL-CIO D.C., Jan 1958--Isard & Fuchs, 1958 (Box 56, Folder 33)
- Core & Boundary of Regional Science (Box 56, Folder 34)
- Zipf & Stewart--Notes & Reprints (Box 56, Folder 35)
- Shale Oil-- Colorado 1957, 1957 (Box 56, Folder 36)
- Isard & Moore-- Regional Science Techniques Applicable to Regional Planning, May 1957, 1957 (Box 56, Folder 37)
- National Bureau Comments on Regional Income Paper, 1955-1956 (Box 56, Folder 38)
- Leontif's Dynamic Model--Notes (Box 56, Folder 39)
- Theory of Games--notes (Box 56, Folder 40)
- Space Monopolitic Competitions & Welfare, 1957 (Box 56, Folder 41)
- Notes on Investment Interviews, 1954 (Box 56, Folder 42)
- AAG 1957--The Balanced Regional Input-Output Model or Device, Descriptive of Nodal Structure (Box 56, Folder 43)
- Notecards (Box 56, Folder 44)
- Cyclopolis--AIP, Chicago, 1977, 1957-1977 (Box 56, Folder 45)
- Why Regional Science? NBER Regional International Conference, June 1955, Duke Univ, 1955 (Box 57, Folder 1)
- Regional Science--Concept of Region, etc. Paper; RSA 1955 NY Mtg., 1955 (Box 57, Folder 2)
- Paper on Theory in Economic Geography, AAG Mtg., 1954 Philadelphia, 1954 (Box 57, Folder 3)
- Comments on Sidney Wolfbein's Paper, IRRA Dec.1953; Economic Consequences of Changing Geography of Industry, 1953 (Box 57, Folder 4)
- Paper AAG Cleveland Mtgs., Spring 1953; Spatial Theory in Ec. Geography, 1953 (Box 57, Folder 5)
- Interdisciplinary Research on Cities--Ideas, Isard 1953, 1953 (Box 57, Folder 6)
- Notes on Harris & VanSick's Paper--Regional Wage Differential, Dec. 1953, 1953 (Box 57, Folder 7)
- Comments of Usher's Paper--national Bureau of Economic Research Capital Formation & Economic Growth (Box 57, Folder 8)
- Introductory Remarks as Chairman of Economic State of New England, AAAS, Dec. 1953, 1953 (Box 57, Folder 9)
- Intermetropolitan Regional Analysis; I-O Approach w/Karesh (Box 57, Folder 10)
- Fairless Steel Worker's Paper--AIP meeting, San Francisco, June 25,1953, 1953 (Box 57, Folder 11)
- NICB Atomic Energy Paper, Oct. 30, 1953, 1953 (Box 57, Folder 12)
- Scientific American Paper, Isard & Whitney, 1953 (Box 57, Folder 13)
- Structure of Regional Economy--Paper to ASS Convention, Urbana, Sept. 1952 or 1953 (Box 57, Folder 14)
- Atomic Energy with Kavesh (Box 57, Folder 15)
- Recent Locational Tendencies--International Dispersion Study, Isard & Kuene, 1952 (Box 57, Folder 16)
- Isard/Ullman Paper AAG, Spring 1957, 1957 (Box 57, Folder 17)
- Human Geography--Some Notes by Isard written for Whittles by 1950-52, 1950-1952 (Box 57, Folder 18)
- Regional Commodity Balance, Interregional Commodity Flows, AEA paper--Dec. 1952, 1952 (Box 57, Folder 19)
- Regional Projections--Milwaukee Paper, Spring 1951; Freutel & Isard, 1951 (Box 57, Folder 20)
- Comment on Gosfield's Paper I-O for Puerto Rico; NBER Conference on Income & Wealth (Box 57, Folder 21)
- Frickey- B & M & The Transport Bldg. Cycle (Box 57, Folder 22)
- Memo on Census Monograph on Location of Economic Activity & Its Relation to Population; Isard--Peck (Box 57, Folder 23)
- Regional I-O paper, Isard & Leontif, Dec. 1950, 1950 (Box 57, Folder 24)
- Toward a More Analytical Economic Geography--AAG 1950, 1951, Isard/Ullman, 1950-1951 (Box 57, Folder 25)
- Frickey-Burns-Mitchell, Input-Output Trend Cycle Problem, 1949 (Box 57, Folder 26)
- AAG Paper Aug. 1952 on Area Research, 1952 (Box 57, Folder 27)
- Current Developments in Regional Economic Analysis, Nov. 1951, Southern Ec. Mtgs.--Isard, 1951 (Box 57, Folder 28)
- Economic Base & Structure of Urban Metropolitan Region--Isard/Kavesh/Kuene (Box 57, Folder 29)
- Metropolitan Site Selection--1948 ?, Isard/Whitney (Box 57, Folder 30)
- MIT Press Corresp. (1), 1965-1976 (Box 57, Folder 31)
- MIT Press Corresp. (2), 1961-1967 (Box 57, Folder 32)
- MIT Press Corresp. (3), 1960-1961 (Box 57, Folder 33)
- MIT Press Corresp. (4), 1967-1970 (Box 57, Folder 34)
- Old MIT Press Corresp. (5), 1955-1959 (Box 57, Folder 35)
- Old MIT Press Corresp. (6), 1959-1960 (Box 57, Folder 36)
- Responses to Questionnaire on a North American Peace Research Society, 1964 (Box 58, Folder 1)
- May--1969, International Peace Academy Program, 1969 (Box 58, Folder 2)
- Correspondence regarding Awards (Contracts), Data (Military Awards) 1962-1963, 1962-1963 (Box 58, Folder 3)
- 1963 Chicago Conference Re: Participation and Attendances, A-D, 1963 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  PRSI
- 1963 PRSI Chicago Conference Re: Participation and Attendance, E to H, 1963 (Box 58, Folder 5)
- 1963 PRSI Chicago Conference Re: Participation and Attendance, I - M, 1963 (Box 58, Folder 6)
- 1963 PRSI Chicago Conference Re: Participation and Attendance, N-S, 1963 (Box 58, Folder 7)
- 1963 PRSI Chicago Conference Re: Participation and Attendance, R-T, 1963 (Box 58, Folder 8)
- 1963 PRSI Chicago Conference Re: Participation and Attendance, U-Z, 1963 (Box 58, Folder 9)
- Vatican Conference--1963, 1963 (Box 58, Folder 10)
- PRSI, 1963-1964 (Box 58, Folder 11)
- Correspondence Re: Peace Research Conferences, 1963-1964 (Box 58, Folder 12)
- Universities--Potential Regional Science Programs 1962-1963, 1962-1963 (Box 58, Folder 13a)
- Berkeley--Regional Science, 1962-1966 (Box 58, Folder 13b)
- Corresp. And Materials Regarding Peace Conferences, 1963-1964 (Box 58, Folder 13c)
- Binghamton--SUNY, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 14)
- Bristol Univ.--England, 1972 (Box 58, Folder 15)
- U of Chicago, 1966 (Box 58, Folder 16)
- Columbia U., 1974 (Box 58, Folder 17)
- Harvard--up to 1966, 1957-1966 (Box 58, Folder 18a)
- Harvard--Misc., 1970 (Box 58, Folder 18b)
- Univ. of Illinois, 1961 (Box 58, Folder 19)
- Indiana Univ., 1966 (Box 58, Folder 20)
- McMaster, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 21)
- Michigan, 1958-1971 (Box 58, Folder 22)
- Univ. of Michigan, 1970, 1970-1971 (Box 58, Folder 23)
- MIT Personal, 1952-1974 (Box 58, Folder 24a)
- MIT --Regional Science, 1957-1972 (Box 58, Folder 24b)
- Netherlands Institute of Economics, 1972 (Box 58, Folder 25)
- Northwestern--Reg. Sci--Moses, 1962-1977 (Box 58, Folder 26)
- Univ. of North Carolina, 1972 (Box 58, Folder 27)
- Ohio State, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 28)
- Univ. of Oregon, 1963 (Box 58, Folder 29)
- U. of Pittsburgh, 1966 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- Princeton Univ.--12/1/71, 1971-1972 (Box 59, Folder 2)
- Purdue, 1961-1962 (Box 59, Folder 3)
- Syracuse, 1973-1974 (Box 59, Folder 4)
- Texas A&M, 1965-166 (Box 59, Folder 5)
- Univ. of Washington, Seattle, 1963-1972 (Box 59, Folder 6)
- Washington U. In St. Louis, 1963 (Box 59, Folder 7)
- U of W. VA, 1966 (Box 59, Folder 8)
- Econ 117--Yale--Reg. Science Seminar, 1960 (Box 59, Folder 9a)
- Yale--Reg. Sci.Program, 1961-1962 (Box 59, Folder 9b)
- Upenn RS Dept., 1958 (Box 59, Folder 10)
- Pre 1960 Resources for Future 1, 1958 (Box 59, Folder 11)
- Pre 1960 Resources for Future 2, 1955-1959 (Box 59, Folder 12)
- Lee Burton, Merrill Lynch, 1954-1955 (Box 59, Folder 13)
- Graham--Regional Economics, U.S. Dept. of Commerce, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 14a)
- Murdock--National Register of Scientific & Technical Personnel, 1963 (Box 59, Folder 14b)
- WI Paper 1960s, 1962 (Box 59, Folder 15)
- Report--Economic Planning Agency & Other Materials, Japan (Box 59, Folder 16)
- UN Africa 1964, 1964-1965 (Box 59, Folder 17)
- Clients EDA Research, 1966-1968 (Box 59, Folder 18)
- CED Area Development Economics, 1959-1960 (Box 59, Folder 19a)
- Faculty Projects, Advisory Committee--Upenn, 1961 (Box 59, Folder 19b)
- ICR Council, 1960 (Box 59, Folder 19c)
- PhD in City Planning--Sept 1960, 1961-1962 (Box 59, Folder 19d)
- OEEC, 1959-1961 (Box 59, Folder 20a)
- OEEC Greek Lectures, 1960-1961 (Box 59, Folder 20b)
- Committee on City Planning & Regional Science, Pre-September 1960, 1957-1960 (Box 59, Folder 21a)
- Fels Fund, 1960 (Box 59, Folder 21b)
- Ford Fellowship, 1959-60, 1958 (Box 59, Folder 21c)
- Regional Science Dept.; Old MIT, Harvard, Chicago, 1947-1957 (Box 59, Folder 21d)
- Operations Research Committee, Upenn 1957-1958, 1957-1958 (Box 59, Folder 22)
- Upenn, 1956-1960 (Box 59, Folder 23)
- Chicago Plan Commission, 1956 (Box 59, Folder 24)
- PhD Program (Box 59, Folder 25)
- O'Leary Life Insurance, 1953-1954 (Box 59, Folder 26)
- Solar Energy--Heat Pricing, 1954 (Box 59, Folder 27)
- Knappen-Tippets-Abbett-McCathy, 1952-1953 (Box 59, Folder 28)
- Research Support--Contracts, 1952-1953 (Box 59, Folder 29)
- Ford Foundation, 1955 (Box 59, Folder 30)
- Ford Foundation Evaluation Letter, 1954-1958 (Box 59, Folder 31)
- Usher's Manuscript Written w/B. Parker, Oct. 1954, 1954 (Box 59, Folder 32)
- Puerto Rico Project--Nucleonics Critique at Millinkan's Seminar, 1957 (Box 59, Folder 33)
- Chamber of Commerce--Greater Philadelphia--Jan 19, 1954, 1954 (Box 59, Folder 34)
- NAM Atomic Energy Talk--Dec. 4, 1953, 1953 (Box 59, Folder 35)
- Population Conference--UN on Nuclear Energy with Whitney- July 1954, 1954 (Box 59, Folder 36)
- Contacts AWR Study Comments, notes on Gulf Coast Trip & Visits to Chemical Companies, 1953 (Box 59, Folder 37)
- St. Lawrence Waterway Report, 1954 (Box 59, Folder 38)
- Starting Point for Econometrica Article, Mathematical idea & Notes on Location & Space Economy (Box 59, Folder 59)
- Regional Development Notes--Chang-Clark-Bean Study (Box 59, Folder 40)
- Economic Relations of PR-US, Project Statement, 1956 (Box 59, Folder 41)
- Linear Programming Notes (Box 60, Folder 1)
- Hansen--Puerto Rico, 1952-1953 (Box 60, Folder 2)
- MIT Conversations, 1955 (Box 60, Folder 3)
- RS 601 Exam--Spring 1962-3, 1962-1963 (Box 60, Folder 4)
- Econ 235a Exam & Grades, 1957-1958 (Box 60, Folder 5)
- Econ. Dept. MIT, Carrothers, 1953-1959 (Box 60, Folder 6)
- Econ 235 Isard Course List--Students, 1951-1952 (Box 60, Folder 7)
- Peace Science --Cornell, 1976 (Box 60, Folder 8a)
- Cornell Univ.--Grad Study in Peace Science Leading to MA & PhD Degrees (Box 60, Folder 8b)
- Peace Science--Penn, 1978 (Box 60, Folder 8c)
- PSSI, 1978-1979 (Box 60, Folder 9a)
- Newsletter, 1972-1973 (Box 60, Folder 9b)
- Journal of Peace Science, 1975-1977 (Box 60, Folder 10a)
- J. of Peace Science--Xeroxed Labels of Libraries (Box 60, Folder 10b)
- Papers, Peace Science Society (International), 1978-1979 (Box 60, Folder 10c)
- Proposal on Journal of Peace Science and Conflict Analysis, 1977 (Box 60, Folder 10d)
- South Asia Office, 1978-1979 (Box 60, Folder 11a)
- WU--Novosibirsk Office, 1978-1979 (Box 60, Folder 11b)
- Correspondence by Date--1978, 1978 (Box 60, Folder 12)
- Correspondence by Date--1/79-2/79, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 13a)
- Correspondence by Date--3/79-4/79, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 13b)
- Correspondence by Date--5/79-7/79, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 14a)
- Correspondence by Date--8/79-11/79, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 14b)
- Correspondence by Date--12/79-2/80, 1979-1980 (Box 60, Folder 15a)
- Correspondence by Date--3/80-4/80, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 15b)
- Correspondence by Date--5/80, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 15c)
- Correspondence--Alphabetical, 1977-1980 (Box 60, Folder 16a)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 60, Folder 16b)
- Misc. Research Proposals 1980, 1979-1980 (Box 60, Folder 17)
- Misc. Notes, 1978-1980 (Box 60, Folder 18a)
- Misc. Notes, 1979-1980 (Box 60, Folder 18b)
- Misc. Asa Project, 1977-1979 (Box 60, Folder 19)
- Correspondence Re. WU International Congress, 1978-1980 (Box 60, Folder 20)
- Post Doctoral Study in Massachusetts @ WU of WRC, Approved 1980, 1974-1980 (Box 60, Folder 21)
- Baker, 1979-1980 (Box 60, Folder 22)
- WU/WAAS Newsletter Materials #2, 1976 (Box 60, Folder 23)
- Copies of RSA Newsletter, 1978-1979 (Box 60, Folder 24)
- WAAS Fellows Responses to 1/24/79 Letter, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 25)
- Walter Fellow's Letters, 1977-1979 (Box 60, Folder 26)
- ICAAS--6/80--Worksheets for Inviting Participants & Building Program, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 27)
- ICAAS--6/80--Preliminary Programs, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 28)
- Regional Science Association, 1977-1979 (Box 60, Folder 29)
- First World Regional Science Congress (Box 60, Folder 30)
- WAAS Executive Committee Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 60, Folder 31)
- WAAS Executive Committee Minutes, 1976-1979 (Box 61, Folder 1)
- WAAS Executive Committee Vitae (Box 61, Folder 2)
- Award--Rufus Jones, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 3)
- Award--Clarence Gamble, 1979-1980 (Box 61, Folder 4)
- WAAS American Division By-Laws, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 5)
- WAAS Manifest, Statutes, 1963 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- WAAS Pamphlets, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 7)
- WU/WAAS Fellows Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 61, Folder 8)
- WAAS--Possible Fellows, 1977 (Box 61, Folder 9)
- WAAS/WU Fellows Mailing List, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 10)
- WAAS Accounts Paid 12-31-79, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 11)
- President WAAS Savings Account--Freedom Federal, 1978-1979 (Box 61, Folder 12)
- WAAS Savings Account.-Cambridge Savings (Clear 4/79), 1977-1978 (Box 61, Folder 13)
- WAAS Checking Account--Charles Bank, 1979-1980 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- WAAs Fellows List 1975, 1977, 1975-1977 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Publishing a Journal--Nancy Meiners, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 16)
- ICAAS Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 61, Folder 17)
- ICAAS Mailing List, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 18)
- ICAAS Registration Forms--Peace Science, Regional Science (Box 61, Folder 19)
- ICAAS 6-1980, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 20)
- Post -Doctoral Candidates, 1968-1969, 1967-1968 (Box 61, Folder 21)
- A-B: Amedeo, Douglas; Balkus, Kosmas, 1967-1969 (Box 61, Folder 22)
- B: Beazely, Ronald; Bossard, Earl, 1968-1970 (Box 61, Folder 23)
- C: Campbell, JM Jr.; Corbin, Peter, 1968-1971 (Box 61, Folder 24)
- C-D: Cox, Milicent Ann, Cummings, Harry s.; Daberkow, Stan G.; Dheter, Aaron, 1969-1971 (Box 61, Folder 25)
- E-G: Eastin, Richard; Fekman, Stephen; Getis, Arthur; Gibbs, Phillip, 1967-1971 (Box 61, Folder 26)
- G-H: Granger, JM; Gray, Charles M; Harms, Louis; Haruta, Hisayoshi, 1968-1969 (Box 61, Folder 27)
- Werczberger Reports (Box 61, Folder 28)
- H-K: Hill, Kenneth D.; Hite, James C.; Mathur, Vijay; Khan, M. Ismail, 1969-1971 (Box 61, Folder 29)
- K-M: Koike, Hirataka;McCarl, Henry, N.; Miller, Dennis W.; Miller, Hugh C.; Miller, Theodore K., 1969-1971 (Box 61, Folder 30)
- O-R: Oyen, Duane Burton; Round, J.I., 1969-1972 (Box 61, Folder 31)
- S: Schultz, George; Six, Xavier; Snarr, Robert T., 1968-1971 (Box 61, Folder 32)
- S-Y: Soedjito, Bambang B.; Stam, Jerome; Stone, Donald; Trusk, Robert; Walter, G.R.; Yamada, H., 1969-1971 (Box 61, Folder 33)
- John Kissin (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Vijay Mathur & Hiroyuki Yamada--Papers, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 2)
- Dave Montgomery--Papers, 1970-1971 (Box 62, Folder 3)
- Duane Shinnick--A.P. Data (Box 62, Folder 4)
- O. Salama--Papers, 1970 (Box 62, Folder 5)
- Jerry Walter--Papers, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 6)
- Jerry Walter--Papers Continued, 1970 (Box 62, Folder 7)
- Elia Werczberger--Papers, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- Hiroyuki Yamada--Paper, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 9)
- Informal Notes--Regional Science Group--April-May 1971, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  Harvard
- HYMP Papers, 1970-1971 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  Harvard, Yale, MIT and Penn
- PL 1-3a--Warntz, 1969-1970 (Box 62, Folder 12)
- R.S. 626, 1969 (Box 62, Folder 13)
- R.S. 251, 1968 (Box 62, Folder 14)
- R.S. 602--Gannon, 1969 (Box 62, Folder 15)
- R.S. 605, 1969 (Box 62, Folder 16)
- R.S. 606--Miller, 1969 (Box 62, Folder 17)
- R.S. 621, 1966 (Box 62, Folder 18)
- R.S. 652, 1972 (Box 62, Folder 19)
- R.S. 601--Gannon, 1969 (Box 62, Folder 20)
- R.S. 205 a,b--Isard New Book (Box 62, Folder 21)
- PL 300 a,b--Woldenberg (Box 62, Folder 22)
- PL 300a-- Schmidt (Box 62, Folder 23)
- PL 8-2ab-- Warntz, 1969 (Box 62, Folder 24)
- R.S. 201-221, 1970-1971 (Box 62, Folder 25a)
- R.S. 201, 1969-1970 (Box 62, Folder 25b)
- R.S. 201, 1967-1971 (Box 62, Folder 25c)
- R.S. 211, 1968-1969 (Box 62, Folder 26)
- R.S. 221, 1969-1970 (Box 62, Folder 27)
- R.S. 271 (Box 62, Folder 28)
- R.S. 251, 1968 (Box 62, Folder 29)
- R.S. 279, 1969-1971 (Box 62, Folder 30a)
- R.S. 279, 1967-1969 (Box 62, Folder 30b)
- R.S. 300 (Box 62, Folder 31)
- R.S. 310, 1970 (Box 62, Folder 32)
- Addresses of Professors & Scholars to Receive Materials (Box 63, Folder 1)
- Administrative Committee R.S. Group: 1969-1970, 1968-1970 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  Regional Science at Harvard
- RS Group--Annual Report, 1969-1970, 1969-1970 (Box 63, Folder 3)
- Committee on Educational Policy, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 4)
- Course Descriptions for Catalogue, 1968-1969 (Box 63, Folder 5)
- Economic-- Ecologic Analysis, 1969-1971 (Box 63, Folder 6)
- EDA--Harvard, Research Contracts, 1968 (Box 63, Folder 7)
- ESSA--Accounting, Correspondence, 1966-7 Progress, Notes on Research Methods, 1966-1970 (Box 63, Folder 8)
- GSD Catalogue Harvard, 1970-71, 1970-1971 (Box 63, Folder 9)
- HUD Reports & Notes (1), 1967 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  New Communities Project
- HUD Reports & Notes (2), 1967-1968 (Box 63, Folder 11)
- HUD Reports & Notes (3), 1967-1968 (Box 63, Folder 12)
- HUD Reports & Notes (4), 1968 (Box 63, Folder 13)
- Landscape Department (Harvard), 1966-1969 (Box 63, Folder 14)
- PRSI Indian Section, 1968-1969 (Box 63, Folder 15)
- PRSI--Tokyo, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 16)
- Planning and Development Committee, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 17)
- Research Office, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 18)
- Ph.D. Program Proposals, 1967 (Box 63, Folder 19)
- Ph.D. City Planning, 1968-1969 (Box 63, Folder 20)
- RSRI Cambridge Reports, Agreement, 1963-1967 (Box 63, Folder 21)
- RS Field Committee Meeting, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 22)
- Regional Science Program Proposal, pre 1969, 1967-1969 (Box 63, Folder 23)
- RS Programs--Memos 1969-71, 1967-1971 (Box 63, Folder 24)
- Resumes, 1968 (Box 63, Folder 25)
- Brown, Jay, 1968-1971 (Box 63, Folder 26)
- Budgets, 1970 (Box 63, Folder 27)
- Harris, Charles, 1966-1969 (Box 63, Folder 28)
- L-S: Lindsey, Jerry; Nash, William; Romanoff, Eli; Sasaki, Hideo, 1967-1971 (Box 63, Folder 29)
- Sert--Doebele Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 63, Folder 30)
- Soltan, Jerzy, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 31a)
- Taylor, Davis, 1967-1969 (Box 63, Folder 31b)
- Vigier, Francois, 1967-1971 (Box 63, Folder 31c)
- Von Moltek, Wilheim, 1967-1968 (Box 63, Folder 31d)
- Kilbridge, 1969-1971 (Box 64, Folder 1)
- Kissen, John, 1968-1971 (Box 64, Folder 2)
- Harvard--PhD Regional Science 1970, 1970 (Box 64, Folder 3)
- Memos--Harvard 1969-71, 1969-1971 (Box 64, Folder 4)
- Correspondence ~1970, Part 1, 1969-1971 (Box 64, Folder 5)
- Correspondence ~ 1970, Part 2, 1969 (Box 64, Folder 6)
- National Science Foundation Research Proposal, Grant --1979, 1979-1983 (Box 64, Folder 7)
- Brookhaven National Laboratory, 1975-1979 (Box 64, Folder 8)
- Oakridge National Laboratory (ORNL), 1976-1978 (Box 64, Folder 9)
- Nova Scotia Project 1979, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 10)
- ORNL Hartsville, Tennessee (Oakridge) 1978, 1976-1979 (Box 64, Folder 11)
- National Coal Assessment, 1976-1977 (Box 64, Folder 12)
- Social, Political & Economic Factors for Impact Analysis 1976, 1976 (Box 64, Folder 13)
- ORNL--proposal 1976, continued 1978, 1976-1978 (Box 64, Folder 14)
- NSF 1972, 1972-1974 (Box 64, Folder 15)
- Misc. Research Proposals --1970s, 1975-1979 (Box 64, Folder 16)
- Energy Research & Development Administration--1974-1975, 1974-1975 (Box 64, Folder 17)
- NSF 1976, 1977, 1978, 1980, 1976-1980 (Box 64, Folder 18)
- NSF/NIH 1976, 1976-1977 (Box 64, Folder 19)
- NSF 1980, 1979-1980 (Box 64, Folder 20)
- WI Book Brochures (Box 64, Folder 21)
- Upenn--RS Brochures, 1963-1979 (Box 64, Folder 22)
- Cornell--RS Brochures, 1973-1978 (Box 64, Folder 23)
- NASA Progress Report 1965, 1965 (Box 64, Folder 24)
- Isard's Appointment books, address books, 1953-1975 (Box 65, Folder 1)
- Lectures & Book Materials on Non-Parametric Statistics (Box 65, Folder 2)
- Math Economics Lectures 1956, 1956 (Box 65, Folder 3)
- Lecture Notes, 1961-1965 (Box 65, Folder 4)
- Lecture Notes 1961-1962, 1961-1962 (Box 65, Folder 5)
- Cornell Lectures--1980s, 1980s (Box 65, Folder 6)
- Space-Time Lecture Notes, 1974-1975 (Box 65, Folder 7)
- Lecture Notes, 1975-1977 (Box 65, Folder 8)
- Misc. Lectures (Time, Relativity, etc.), 1971-1973 (Box 65, Folder 9)
- Parson--Notes & Ideas of WI (Material to be Included in General Equilibrium Chapter) (Box 65, Folder 10)
- ? Tokyo Presentation? 1960? (Box 65, Folder 11)
- Lecture Notes (Box 65, Folder 12)
- Lecture Notes--Introduction to Peace Science 1968- 1970, 1968-1970 (Box 65, Folder 13)
- Lecture Notes, 1961-1963 (Box 65, Folder 14)
- Lecture Notes--RS 661: Regional Social Science Theory, 1961-1964 (Box 65, Folder 15)
- Lecture Notes, 1961-1963 (Box 65, Folder 16)
- Philadelphia Region Input-Output Working Papers, Vol. III & IV, Langford & Isard, 1967 (Box 66, Folder Item 1)
- Philadelphia Region Input-Output Study Working Papers, Vol. 1 &2, 1966 (Box 66, Folder Item 2)
- Environment and Society in Transition: World Priorities, 1975 (Box 66, Folder Item 3)
- Regional Science and Landscape Analysis Project (Box 66, Folder Item 4)
- Ecologic-Economic Analysis For Regional Development, 1968 (Box 66, Folder Item 5)
- Preliminary Assessment of a Hypothetical Nuclear Energy Center in New Jersey, 1975 (Box 66, Folder Item 6)
- Regional Science & Research on Environmental Management, WI (Box 66, Folder 7)
- Regional Economic Impacts of Nuclear Power Plants, 1976 (Box 66, Folder Item 8)
- Regional Economic Impacts of Nuclear Energy Centers, RS Upenn 1957, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 9)
- Regional Economic Impacts of Nuclear Power Plants, RS Upenn 1976, 1976 (Box 66, Folder 10)
- Draft--Issues in Clustered Nuclear Siting, 1976 (Box 66, Folder Item 11)
- Regional Economic Impacts of Nuclear Power Plants, 1976 (Box 66, Folder Item 12)
- Socio-Economic Impact Analysis of Energy Facilities with Particular Reference to the Hartville, Tennessee, Impact Area, 1977 (Box 66, Folder Item 13)
- Stochastic Control and Multilevel Coordination Models for Air Quality Management Within a Region, 1971 (Box 66, Folder Item 14)
- Market Systems for the Control of Air Pollution, 1971 (Box 66, Folder Item 15)
- Brookhaven Project 1976, 1976 (Box 67, Folder 1)
- Brookhaven 1979, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 2)
- A Case Study of the Watertown Region--WI, 1972-1973 (Box 67, Folder 3)
- EPA 1973, Part A, 1972-1973 (Box 67, Folder 4)
- EPA 1973, Part B, 1972-1973 (Box 67, Folder 5)
- EPA 1973, Part C, 1973 (Box 67, Folder 6)
- Notes for EPA Report, 1973 (Box 67, Folder 7)
- Second Quarterly Report, 1973 (Box 67, Folder 8)
- National Science Foundation Grant, DA 4402, 1974 (Box 67, Folder 9)
- Correspondence with Margaret Windus, 1973-1975 (Box 67, Folder 10)
- Research Proposal to NSF/ "A Cross-Policy Study of Tech Innov.", 1974 (Box 67, Folder 11)
- First Quarterly Report, Grant DA --44041, 9/74, 1974 (Box 67, Folder 12)
- Report--Grant DA--4402, 5/31/75, 1975 (Box 67, Folder 13)